CANDIDATE RESUME

Clinton Lombard

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 22 May 1995

Residential Area: Cape Town

Languages: English And Afrikaans

Contact +27 677128304 Lombardclinton40@gmail.com

Education

Called For Change Bible InstituteDegree in Theology

Crestway High SchoolNational Senior Certificate

Online Presence

LinkedIn: Clinton Lombard | LinkedIn Github: Your Repositories (github.com)

Portfolio (clintonlombard.netlify.app)

Key Skills

Microsoft Office
Efficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python &
Java
Collaboration: Teamwork
Planning and organization skills
Knowledge of Sports and Fitness
Team Work
Percerverance and Patience

Interests & Hobbies

Designing Websites / Reading Hiking / Playing Soccer Cooking And Traveling

About me

I have 9 years of sales experience and 5 years of IT knowledge. I am also eager to expand my skills and obtain more experience at work. I am a junior software developer with a commitment to constant learning. I am always eager to learn new technologies and enhance my knowledge of coding. CSS, JavaScript, HTML, and Python are all skills I've gained through training and learning. My coaching philosophy focuses on encouraging teamwork, discipline, and perseverance while creating a welcoming environment that fosters personal development.

Achievements & Key Projects

Worked on a group project and done a financial calculator.
Own clothing business / Printing / Embroidery
Got best coach of the year.
Certificate for leadership
Degree in Theology

Work Experience

Software Developer UVU Africa - Intern Nov 2023 – Present Cape Town, Western Cape, South Afrika

Crestway High School Sports Coach 23 January 2023 – 30 September 2023

Sell Direct Marketing Call Centre Consultant January 2015-April 2021

References

Afika Maliwa

Candidate Success Manager

Afika.Maliwa@capaciti.org.za

Contact Details: +27 78 692 2178